L: The Highland Hotel’s twenty miles from here.
M: Fine. No problem. Let’s go there.
L: Yes. Alfie’s asleep now.
M: Great.
L: Mel! Look! A police car!
M: OK, OK.
P: Good evening. Turn off the engine, please. Thank you.
Can I see your driving licence? Thank you.
M: What’s the problem, officer?
P: One of your back lights isn’t on.
M: Oh dear. I’m very sorry, officer.
We’re on our way to the Highland Hotel. We’re very near now. And we’re with a baby.
P: Ah, what a beautiful baby! What’s his name?
L: Alfie.
P: Oh dear, sorry! OK… go to your hotel. But please drive very slowly.
And fix your light. There’s a garage near the hotel.
M: Yes – thank you, officer.
P: Goodbye. Goodbye, Alfie!
M: Good boy, Alfie.